Hey everyone. Uh yesterday I was doing a
long run from uh Shamon from Kurmayet to
Shamuni to see how uh my knee were
reacting uh on a on a long run like
that. After a few weeks uh of good
training uh home and uh mostly we have
decided with the medical team to to have
an approach conservative approach uh of
the injury to to try to to save all the
cartilage and and and try with uh with
the management of the load. But I I saw
that after 5 hours where I was feeling
very good that the the pain and all the
instability and the problem started to
to be again there. So I decide not to
not to run at UTV um this year and uh
focus on like having a uh yeah some
intervention to to solve the problem for
uh for good and to um to focus on next
winter and uh and and the next summer
for the for the racing and the all the
other goals. Anyway, it will be super
fun to be here to share on everybody. It
will be an exciting race. Uh first this
weekend I made racing at Kima and then
next week with all the friends here at
tombb.